I've spent the last three
or four weeks traveling overseas,
and I've not really put
out any content whatsoever. If anything,
I've completely neglected my
business. Probably thinking, why
are you recording in your car to begin
with?
But very good reason.
[car revving] It's called an appeal to
authority.
You see, the classic villain arc online
is that you do well in business, then you
start teaching people how to do well in
business, and the majority of people doing
that are fucking pathetic.
And I'm definitely not the richest content
creator out of all the people you follow
online, or that would be a GT3 RS,
and I only got the GT3.
Now,
I'm going to put some of our new flavor of
Nutonic in the fridge, and then I'm
going to explain to you how I still
managed to make over $100,000 this month
without posting on social media.
And the best part yet
is you don't even need to
have your own fancy gym,
or your own sauna,
or even your own dream car.
Well, truth be told,
it's actually not my dream car because I
never thought I'd
ever be able to have a car like this in my
life.
I was dreaming about an Audi RS6,
but we got a little bit carried away.
All you need is one of the things I'm
holding here, an iPhone, a good computer,
ideally a MacBook Pro, and a tripod.
Right.
Let's get out of this shitty production.
Let's crack on.
Now,
isn't this a nicer technical setup for us
to talk about what we're going to
talk about today? So
if we go to month to date for this date,
we can
see that we're at $113,000.
Now, if we go over to YouTube,
we can have a little look
that I haven't posted in
24 days and 16 hours. Now, my YouTube
is the main place that I get
sales for my mentorship program
and all the little courses around it.
And I'm going to explain to you some very
simple systems you can put in place to
earn you money whilst you do other things
more important than churning out content
every day. [can opening]
Just before we get into that,
we have a look at RevTrack here.
Very good platform software.
You can see every single video
that I've done.
I can look at the revenue that's been
attributed to it.
For instance, this video did $12,700,
and I can also see which
courses came from it,
whether it's Business Mentorship,
Content Mastery, Email
Advantage, or my PT Starter Kit.
Now I know that's my best performing
video.
It's probably going to make sense for me
to loop you into that at the end of this.
So just before we get to my end card at
the end of the video, if you're ever
wondering why some creators
are pointing you in the direction of a
certain video,
it's usually the one that's generating the
most revenue.
Now,
you'll notice there's a discrepancy here
between the clicks and the revenue.
There's what? Under 50 sales,
and there's 2,558 clicks.
What does that mean? Well,
it means not every link
that I put in a video is about
making a sale.
Sometimes there's a much better use of
someone's click that doesn't
result in asking them to buy a product.
And that's the point of this video.
So when I am on social media
and I have the pleasure of making content
like today,
my sole objective of a video
is often to put someone into a lead
magnet.
But it's not just a lead magnet.
It's not just, "Hey, guys,
download my free
asset." I'm actually going to push people
into an email automation where on
different days, one after another,
they're going to receive a very helpful
email from me, and at some point,
some of those people are going to buy,
some of
them won't. In front of me right here
is one of the best
and easiest ones in which
I've used.
This then nurtures someone over 30 days to
give them 30 different ways
they can improve their business.
I know a lot of people
are going to get this and
think, "Oh,
I bet the information in there
is not even that good." And they might
sign up anyway just to figure out how it
is I'm making sales, and I implore you to
do the same. In this video,
don't just listen to what I'm saying.
You should have a look at what I do so you
can copy it.
Now,
all of these links will be in the
description,
and I'll be able to see all of
them on RevTrack, which is awesome.
And just before we get into the next one,
there's a little thing that I should get
off my chest that a lot of creators
and people in my position don't because
they
make a benefit from lying to you about
stuff.
So last week, sat down with the team
that helped me operate my business, and we
could see that there
was $110,000 of revenue. So people think,
"Oh, that's amazing.
That's all money in your pocket." Not
quite.
If you look here,
we spent $37,000 in ad spend, and you
can see the performance
is down week on week.
You can see that we spent 37,
nearly $38,000 in ad rev.
And as you can see, our ROAS,
our return on ad spend,
and our advertising revenue
is down a lot. This
is because we've taken some new products,
and we're starting to
put them out there to cold audiences,
so they just can't perform as well as
possible.
So even though I say I made $110,000,
when you reduce
the 40 from that, it's closer to 70.
Revenue is not profit.
Revenue is not what you get to keep.
And I think it's sometimes disingenuous
for people to throw around numbers
when the
reality is they're not keeping all of it.
Now, as you can see here,
I've got several different email marketing
flows working
at different points. We've got some
that are paid, some that are organic,
some from
different flows. Now,
what I'm going to do
is I'm just going to protect the revenue
splits and the open rates
and the click rates here just to keep a
bit of curiosity.
I'm showing you how the sausage is made,
but I don't want you to know exactly how
my business operates,
or you might copy the right things
and potentially put me out
of business. Who knows? But every week,
we track different performances of
different lead magnets so we can know
where to focus attention for the following
week. So the 30 days
and 30 ways organic content we send there
does pretty
well. Paid content
that we send there doesn't often perform
as well because we're
almost having to pay someone to get them
onto it.
They're probably not as warm as say, you,
the viewer watching this video.
People that are coming in through YouTube
videos just probably have seen more raw
hours of me talking to camera,
so they probably trust me better,
and they're more
inclined to buy and trust me.
Then I realized in my RevTrack data
that the majority
of my sales were coming from videos where
I was speaking about landing pages.
Landing pages are websites
that you send people to to buy a product.
And I've realized that
when I work with people inside my Discord,
one of the main
places of contention is landing pages,
how people are structuring their sales
page,
getting their offer across.
So I thought that I would make a template,
which I did.
Now, that's not the whole thing. That
is just kind of a visual asset, and I
thought it could help if I
was to hold up something
and point to it in ads, which
it does perform very, very well. So
when people sign up here, name, email,
they
get sent the asset,
but then I put them into an email
automation.
I believe this one is between five
and ten days.
Each day, because they get the asset,
they enjoy the asset, and then they think,
"Oh, yeah, I'm not quite convinced."
And the next day I come in, boom, hit them
with another fact they didn't know.
Then the next day, boom.
By day five, they're probably thinking,
"Bloody hell, this guy really knows a lot
about sales pages."
And although my main product is $3,500 US,
which is a
lot of money, I always remind people
that if all your existing efforts
are going to
a sales page and you're getting a 1%
conversion, some simple tweaks to that
landing page could take you to 2%. Now,
1% to 2% doesn't sound like a lot,
but it would double the amount of revenue
that you're getting from the existing
amount of work. So think about that.
Same amount of posts on socials,
same amount of call to action,
same amount of
hours spending online,
same amount of time in the edit,
same amount in every single
component, but you improve that,
and you get more money from the same
effort.
Now,
people from this definitely convert better
than the 30 days, but again, I
think it's because their needs
are different.
From the 30 days, 30 ways,
I get some people to do my courses like
the Short Form
Content Mastery. The people that
are struggling from their sales page
are often
larger,
much more established business with higher
needs.
So I'd say I get more mentorship sales
from that lead magnet than I do the other.
Now, this is a very interesting one.
In some of my content,
including the most recent video,
even though looking at it,
the views may not seem
that impressive My main call to action
is to say to people,
"Hey, give me your email address
and I will add you to the next video."
Now,
we will have to blur this out for data
protection, but if we
go and look, even in the last 30 days,
there have been
dozens of people that
are applying for this web critique.
Now,
this is where I go into to pick people to
use in the next videos.
But here's the interesting part.
Once they opt in to have their content
critiqued, which you guys can do, again,
with the link in the description to this
video,
I then chuck them into the 30-day
automation of "30 Ways in 30 Days." You
can see here. "Either way,
I'll check in with you in the next 30
days." For some
reason, that reason I actually don't know,
people that enter the 30-day
automation from this lead magnet attribute
double the sales per
person. Double. And I don't even know why.
So 500 people going through this equates
to the same rev as
1,000 people going through the 30-day
automation.
Now, not all of these lead magnets
that I used work within business to
business.
So some of you may have noticed
that recently I started TRT about a year
ago, and
although it's not been great for my
hairline, you'll notice
that I'm more jacked,
I'm leaner, I train more,
I compete more in jujitsu.
I'm generally day to day just more
aggressive.
Not like I want to fight people.
I'm like, "Let's go, brother.
Let's ho." It's the testosterone.
So I've started and I've invested into a
company called Manual in the UK.
I'm now helping men get their blood work
checked.
So I bought the domain,
checkyourblood.com.
And let's say you're in the UK
or Northern Ireland.
I am then using another page to take your
data to put you into an
email automation. And
that email automation just tells you about
the TRT process,
about how often to inject,
what you can expect, what the pros are.
Are there any cons?
Because I don't just want to give someone
a little PDF about,
"Oh,
here's a PDF cheat sheet on TRT." I want
to be able to hit you with some
nuance every single day,
because my call to action on this
is to get people to
order a blood test. Now,
I don't get paid if they order a blood
test or not, but
it's sometimes just silly to expect
someone to just think, "Oh,
buy blood test.
Fine." I want to email them the day after
the blood test arrives and the day after
that and to say, "Hey, mate.
Bloody get your blood work checked."
And the reason I
get their phone number
is I can look at the data in the back end
of people that
have bought tests and not done it yet.
So then I can ping them
and nurture them and say, "Hey, Dave.
Do your flipping blood test. Send it back.
Let's see how you're at." So every single
call to action in which I'm utilizing
online revolves around the purpose of
putting someone to an email automation.
That means at any given point,
I could be walking down the street
and someone could
go, "Hey, James. That email
that you put out today was sick,"
and I have no idea
what they're talking about.
And that's what I want people to do.
And I don't just want it to be one lead
magnet for your business.
So you can see here,
I'm operating five at the same time,
all based on different
needs and wants that people have. And
if nine out of 10 people go through the
automation and do nothing with it,
that's fine.
The purpose is that one out of 10 people
will take action from those emails, and
it's because I made the effort to touch
base every day.
Even though they know it's an automation,
it's just that little bit more effort
that I think is crucial to put in
when it comes to trying to get someone to
trust
you enough to buy your stuff. Now,
as you will remember, RevTrack,
the highest
revenue video,
was the laziest way to make money.
So I can go over to this,
have a look at my content. Where is she?
And now because I know this video
is doing really well
and for getting loads and
loads of people to buy loads of things
that I'm doing.
Oh, I've just seen Dan Martell.
I never saw this. Mate, I love your stuff.
I am a big fan boy.
For any of you who don't know,
Dan Martell, not only is he a
legend,
not only did he invest into Nu Tonic,
embarrassingly, I only saw a
video last night. There's this video
that I've seen of this guy walking his
member of staff around a sports car just
like mine downstairs.
Very similar spec. And he goes, "Oh,
isn't this the car that you've got on the
background of your phone?"
And the guy's like, "Yeah."
And then he buys it from
him. Last night, I realized that
was Dan Martell.
I've been Dan Martell's biggest fan.
I've seen that video,
but because he's wearing a hat,
I never noticed it was him.
And I'll be honest with you.
One of my dream goals in life
is to get so rich,
not even for me.
I just want to be able to buy stuff for my
mates.
"Oh,
I seen you double tapped a reel of
that car.
I've bought you it." "Oh,
I heard your nan's going to a home.
I paid for it." "Oh,
heard you're flying to America in economy.
I've upgraded you." They're the goals.
Or to take your best friends on a private
jet so I'd be there for 24 hours, which I
did last weekend. But this
is pure distraction.
The point I'm trying to get to is this.
Once you make a video like this with the
objection of getting people to click your
lead magnets, we must be prepared
that not everyone is going to be ready to
click
on that lead magnet into action with it.
So the best thing we can do
is to point them in a direction like
this and open another hook. But
if you're someone that's too lazy to put
together
lead magnets and put them all over the
internet to get people to sign up, imagine
if there was a way
that you could make more money doing even
less work than the
things I spoke about in this video.
And if you click this one right here,
you'll find out all about it.
And that is how you make money without
having to post videos all the time.